http://www.tendocom.com/privacy-policy/

Search TendoSearch this website Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to footerWho We AreOur website address is: http://tendocom.com.What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect ItCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact FormsWe collect your personal data through form submissions. You will know what information you give us, because you’ll type it into the form. The reason for collecting the data should be self-evident for each specific form. If you have any concerns with what information is collected or why, do not submit the form.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded Content from Other WebsitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsThe information collected is for statistical, communication, and customer service purposes only. We may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we use software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.Who We Share Your Data WithWe do not sell your data to any third party. We will not share you data with any third party who is not directly involved in the operations of our business, like vendors including our website development team, for example.Tendo keeps information about all site visitors—including clients and their customers—strictly confidential. We will never sell or disclose any information that identifies you to unrelated third parties without prior authorization. So, relax, your clicks are safe with us.Occasionally, we do reveal general statistical information about our website and visitors, such as the number of visitors or page views, but, we’ll say it one more time: We never reference or identify specific visitors without explicit permission.How Long We Retain Your DataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What Rights You Have Over Your DataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where We Send Your DataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your Contact InformationIf you have any questions or feedback regarding our privacy policy, please email us at inquiries@tendocom.com.FooterLinkedInTwitterFacebookinquiries@tendocom.comStay CurrentSubscribe to the Tendo View Newsletter to get insights on topics and trends that affect your content marketing and communication programs SubscribeNewsletterFirst Name*Last Name*Email* CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Get In TouchTendo Communications San Francisco Office 535 Mission St., 19th Floor San Francisco, CA 94105Washington DC Office 1775 Tysons Blvd., 5th Floor McLean, VA 22102Phone: 415.369.8200 Fax: 415.369.8222Briefly NotedContent marketing #metrics 101: a intro to 9 KPIs every #marketer should know via @ukuinbound tendo.cm/37YA9BM #contentmarketingYesterday at 10:00 pm
Friend's email
Message https://tendocom.com/privacy-policy/ Send
ServicesContent Strategy & ExperienceContent MarketingWorkBlogResourcesContent Best PracticesContent GlossaryCompanyCareersContactSearch
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkNo Cookies for MePrivacy Policy
